upcleaner.net 2016-09-08

# PRIVACY POLICY

WWW.GREENET.XYZ'S PRIVACY POLICY

www.greenet.xyz is committed to protecting your privacy online. To further this commitment, we have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information collected about you online.

**WHAT INFORMATION DOES WWW.GREENET.XYZ COLLECT?**

www.greenet.xyz may request and/or collect information from you on a voluntary basis when you: register with us, or when you send questions or comments via e-mail to www.greenet.xyz customer support. The requested information may include personal information such as your name and e-mail address.

If you are under the age of 13, you will need your parent or guardian's consent before you can provide any personal information to us for purposes of registration and other online activities.

**SIGN UP TO OUR FREE NEWSLETTER**

If you wish to sign up to our free newsletter, you will be asked to supply personal information such as your e-mail address. With your permission, www.greenet.xyz uses such information to periodically contact you with product information news, special offers and new games that are released.

**E-MAIL**

By allowing you to send e-mail to us, we are not attempting to collect any personal information about you. We will only use personal information (such as name and e-mail address) contained in your e-mail to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the e-mail. Although we may retain your e-mail for a period of time, we will not use any personal information contained in your e-mail for any purpose other than responding to your specific inquiry or comments. Whatever the activity may be, we will only collect information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives.

**OPT OUT**

If you are receiving e-mails or regular mail and at a later date you choose to opt out and have your name removed from the e-mailing list, you can do so by using the link included with a www.greenet.xyz e-mail.

**COOKIES**

www.greenet.xyz may use cookies to improve the use of our websites. A "cookie" is a small file that websites often store on a user's computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our websites. For example, cookies allow us to remember your screen name, tell us that you have visited our website before, and may contain information that will make your next visit to our website more enjoyable. However, we do not use cookies to store personal information such as your name. In addition, www.greenet.xyz does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.

Additionally, www.greenet.xyz may use cookies and third party vendors to deliver ads related to www.greenet.xyz to you while you are surfing other websites.

**IP ADDRESSES**

www.greenet.xyz may also collect your IP address for safety and security purposes. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.

**LOG FILES**

Other non-personal information collected by www.greenet.xyz is in the form of logs - files that record website activity, including how many "hits" a particular web page is getting (a.k.a., "click-through data"). For example, log file entries are generated every time a visitor clicks the "Home" icon on our site. These entries enable www.greenet.xyz to assess overall site activity, track interest in advertised sales, track interest in purchase behavior, and troubleshoot technical concerns. Through the use of log files, we may also collect certain demographic information such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

**LINKING TO THIRD PARTY SITES**

To provide relevant information not found on our Web site, www.greenet.xyz may provide links from our Web sites to third party Web sites and we encourage our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information. All the downloads and Exe files provided on this site are from a 3rd party and www.greenet.xyz is not responsible for any files or adware that gets installed by their games and screensavers. They contain several adware products so download and install at your own risk. www.greenet.xyz assumes NO responsibility. www.greenet.xyz is not responsible for the privacy practices of the content of third party sites'. www.greenet.xyz hereby disclaims any representations or warranties expressed on any site other than its own site.

**WHO IS COLLECTING MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Any personal information that you disclose while visiting any of our websites is collected by www.greenet.xyz, and is used in the manner specified above.

By using this site, you signify your assent to the www.greenet.xyz Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes.

Some of the web search services provided herein are provided by Trovi Search and powered by Trovi search partners. For information on the web search services data collection, please visit <http://info.trovi.com/Privacy>, and the search provider's privacy policy, as applicable.

**How to Contact Esoffers.**

If you have any concerns or questions with respect to any matter covered by this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by email at: [bd@esoffers.com](mailto:bd@esoffers.com) or at the following address:

ESOffers Network Co., Limited

Rm 1205, 12/F,

Tai SangBank Building,

130-132DesVoeux Road，Central,

Hong Kong

Phone Number: +85 231733712
